Finding aid to Honorary Degree Files CA.MS.00006
Smith College Archives
Honorary Degree Files
1886-1994
Smith College Archives
Smith College.
CA.MS.00006
4.458 linear feet (9 containers)
Contains press releases, newspaper clippings, photographs, correspondence, as well as biographical information on those awarded the honorary degree, and information about the particular Commencement when the degree was awarded.
Scope and Contents
The Honorary Degree files contain press releases, newspaper clippings, photographs, and correspondence concerning the process of awarding the honorary degree at Smith, as well as biographical information on those awarded the honorary degree, and information about the particular Commencement when the degree was awarded. These files were maintained by the Office of Public Relations, as well as the Office of the Board of Trustees and transferred over a period of years.
This collection is organized into five series:
I: Chronological Files
II. Individual Files
III. Board of Trustees - Committee on Honorary Degrees
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Source unknown.
Degrees, Academic--Massachusetts--Northampton.; Smith College--Degrees.; Smith College. Board of Trustees. Committee on Honorary Degrees.
- Series I. Chronological Files - General information
  - 1910-11 (Box 79)
  - 1913-14 (Box 79)
  - 1920-21 (Box 79)
  - 1924-25 (Box 79)
  - 1925-26 (Box 79)
  - 1926-27 (Box 79)
  - 1927-28 (Box 79)
  - 1928-29 (Box 79)
  - 1929-30 (Box 79)
  - 1930-31 (Box 79)
  - 1931-32 (Box 79)
  - 1932-33 (Box 79)
  - 1933-34 (Box 79)
  - 1935-36 (Box 79)
  - 1936-37 (Box 79)
  - 1937-38 (Box 79)
  - 1938-39 (Box 79)
  - 1939-40 (Box 79)
  - 1940-41 (Box 79)
  - 1942-43 (Box 79)
  - 1943-44 (Box 79)
  - 1944-45 (Box 79)
  - 1945-46 (Box 79)
  - 1946-47 (Box 79)
  - 1947-48 (Box 79)
  - 1948-49 (Box 79)
  - 1950-51 (Box 79)
  - 1951-52 (Box 79)
  - 1952-53 (Box 79)
  - 1953-54 (Box 79)
  - 1954-55 (Box 79)
  - 1955-56 (Box 79)
  - 1956-57 (Box 79)
  - 1957-58 (Box 79)
  - 1958-59 (Box 79)
  - 1959-60 (Box 79)
  - 1960-61 (Box 79)
  - 1961-62 (Box 79)
  - 1962-63 (Box 79)
  - 1963-64 (Box 79)
  - 1964-65 (Box 79)
  - 1965-66 (Box 79)
  - 1966-67 (Box 79)
  - 1967-68 (Box 79)
  - 1968-69 (Box 79)
  - 1969-70 (Box 79)
  - 1970-71 (Box 79)
  - 1971-72 (Box 79)
  - 1972-73 (Box 79)
  - 1973-74 (Box 79)
  - 1974-75 (Box 79)
  - 1975-76 (Box 79)
  - 1976-77 (Box 79)
  - 1978-79 (Box 79)
  - 1980-81 (Box 79)
  - 1982-83 (Box 79)
  - 1983-84 (Box 79)
  - 1985-86 (Box 79)
  - 1987-88 (Box 79)
  - 1990-91 (Box 79)
  - 1991-92 (Box 79)
  - 1994- (Box 79)
- Series II. Alphabetical Files - Honorary Degree Recipients
  - Abbott, Berenice - DFA, 1973 (Box 80)
  - Addams, Jane - LLD, 1910 (Box 80)
  - Allen, Hope Emily - LHD, 1946 (Box 80)
  - Anderson, Marian - MUSD, 1944 (Box 80)
  - Angelou, Maya - LittD, 1975 (Box 80)
  - Anderson, Mary - LLD, 1941 (Box 80)
  - Arendt, Hannah - LLD, 1966 (Box 80)
  - Atwood, Margaret - LittD, 1982 (Box 80)
  - Barranechea, Ana Maria - LittD, 1967 (Box 80)
  - Barrow, Dame Ruth Nita - LLD, 1991 (Box 80)
  - Baumgartner, Leona - ScD, 1956 (Box 80)
  - Beard, Mary R. - LLD, 1945 (Box 80)
  - Begtrup, Bodil - LLD, 1949 (Box 80)
  - Bequignon-Lagarde, Charlotte - LLD, 1949 (Box 80)
  - Berendsen, Mildred Jeanmarie - LHD, 1991 (Box 80)
  - Bishop, Elizabeth - LittD, 1968 (Box 80)
  - Blanding, Sarah Gibson - LLD, 1949 (Box 80)
  - Boardman, Mabel Thorpe - LLD, 1916 (Box 80)
  - Boggs, Jean Sutherland - LLD, 1975 (Box 80)
  - Boulanger, Nadia - DFA, 1958 (Box 80)
  - Blanchard, Elizabeth - AM, 1888 (Box 80)
  - Bree, Germaine - LittD, 1960 (Box 80)
  - Bunting, Mary I. - LLD, 1960 (Box 80)
  - Burbridge, Eleanor Margaret Peachey - ScD, 1963 (Box 80)
  - Caldwell, Sarah - DFA, 1974 (Box 80)
  - Cam, Helen Maud - LLD, 1949 (Box 80)
  - Carmirelli, Pina - MusD, 1982 (Box 80)
  - Carson, Rachel - LittD, 1953 (Box 80)
  - Cather, Willa Sibert - LHD, 1933 (Box 80)
  - Chan, Palay '65, 1979 (Box 80)
  - Chisholm, Shirley - LLD, 1975 (Box 80)
  - Clapp, Margaret - LLD, 1949 (Box 80)
  - Cleary, Catherine Blanchard - LLD, 1973 (Box 80)
  - Conte, Silvio O. - LLD, 1991 (Box 80)
  - Cook, Constance Eberhardt - LLD, 1971 (Box 80)
  - Coolidge, Elizabeth Sprague - AM, 1927 (Box 80)
  - Coolidge, Grace Goodhue - LLD, 1929 (Box 80)
  - Cooney, Joan Ganz - LLD, 1986 (Box 80)
  - Cori, Gerty T. - ScD, 1949 (Box 80)
  - Cornell, Catherine - LHD, 1937 (Box 80)
  - Cowles, Louise Frances - AM, 1893 (Box 80)
  - Cromwell, Otelia - LLD, 1950 (Box 80)
    - Cromwell, Otelia - LLD: Correspondence, 1940-50 (Box 80)
  - Crosby, Elizabeth Caroline - ScD, 1967 (Box 80)
  - Crowdy, Dame Rachel Eleanor - LLD, 1926 (Box 80)
  - Curie, Marie Sklodowska - ScD, 1921 (Box 80)
    - Curie, Marie Sklodowska - ScD: Photos
  - D'Alverny, Marie Therese - LittD, 1977 (Box 80)
  - Dean, Vera Micheles - LLD, 1944 (Box 80)
  - Del Mundo, Fe - ScD, 1970 (Box 80)
  - De Mille, Agnes George - LHD, 1954 (Box 81)
  - De Valois, Dame Ninette - DFA, 1957 (Box 81)
  - Donhoff, Marion Grafin - LHD, 1962 (Box 81)
  - Draper, Ruth - LHD, 1947 (Box 81)
  - Dresselhaus, Mildred - ScD, 1980 (Box 81)
  - Drinker, Sophie - MusD, 1949 (Box 81)
  - Edelman, Marian Wright - LLD, 1969 (Box 81)
  - Edwards, Amelia Blanford - LLD, 1886 (Box 81)
  - Eliot, Martha May - ScD, 1949 (Box 81)
  - Farrand, Beatrix Codwalader Jones, 1936 (Box 81)
  - Feng, Yen-Tsai - LHD, 1982 (Box 81)
  - Fermin-Gomes, Mercedes - LLD, 1970 (Box 81)
  - Fichandler, Zelda - DFA, 1977 (Box 81)
  - Fieser, Mary Peters - ScD, 1969 (Box 81)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield - LHD, 1954 (Box 81)
  - Fiske, Minnie Maddern - AM, 1926 (Box 81)
  - Flanner, Janet - LittD, 1958 (Box 81)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen - DFA, 1973 (Box 81)
  - Gaposchkin, Cecilia Payne - ScD, 1951 (Box 81)
  - Gilbreth, Lillian Moller - ScD, 1945 (Box 81)
  - Gildersleeve, Virginia Crocheron - LHD, 1936 (Box 81)
  - Giovanni, Nikki - LittD, 1975 (Box 81)
  - Gleason, Catherine Crozier - MusD, 1965 (Box 81)
  - Gleditsch, Ellen - ScD, 1914 (Box 81)
  - Gordimer, Nadine - LittD, 1985 (Box 81)
  - Graham, Katherine - LLD, 1975 (Box 81)
  - Graham, Martha - DFA, 1969 (Box 81)
  - Fell, Honor Bridget - ScD, 1962 (Box 81)
  - Granville, Evelyn Boyd - ScD, 1989 (Box 81)
  - Grasso, Ella Tambussi - LLD, 1976 (Box 81)
  - Griffiths, Martha Wright - LLD, 1976 (Box 81)
  - Grosman, Tatyana - DFA, 1973 (Box 81)
  - Hagen, Uta - DFA, 1978 (Box 81)
  - Hall, Helen - LHD, 1969 (Box 81)
  - Hamilton, Alice - ScD, 1927 (Box 81)
  - Hamilton, Gordon - LHD, 1953 (Box 81)
  - Hanks, Nancy - LHD, 1978 (Box 81)
  - Hardwick, Elizabeth - LittD, 1975 (Box 81)
  - Harris, Julie - AM, 1956 (Box 81)
  - Harris, Patricia Roberts - LLD, 1974 (Box 81)
  - Harris, Rosemary - DFA, 1968 (Box 81)
  - Harrison, Anna - ScD, 1975 (Box 81)
  - Hartridge, Emelyn Battersby - LHD, 1928 (Box 81)
  - Hayes, Helen - LHD, 1940 (Box 81)
  - Height, Dorothy Irene - LittD, 1975 (Box 81)
  - Hellman, Lillian - LittD, 1974 (Box 81)
  - Henderson, Julia Juanita - LLD, 1967 (Box 81)
  - Hewitt, Helen Margaret - LittD, 1968 (Box 81)
  - Himmelfarb, Gertrude - LittD, 1977 (Box 81)
  - Hirsch, Katrina de, 1984 (Box 81)
  - Hobby, Oveta Culp - LLD, 1954 (Box 81)
  - Hoffleit, E. Dorrit - ScD, 1984 (Box 81)
    - Hoffleit, E. Dorrit - ScD: Clippings, awards, etc.
    - Hoffleit, E. Dorrit - ScD: Publications
  - Hoffman, Malvina - LHD, 1951 (Box 81)
  - Holtzman, Elizabeth - LLD, 1982 (Box 81)
  - Hopper, Grace Murray - LLD, 1984 (Box 81)
  - Homer, Louise - AM, 1931 (Box 81)
  - Horner, Matina Souretis - LLD, 1979 (Box 81)
  - Hortsmann, Dorothy Millicent - ScD, 1961 (Box 81)
  - Howe, Julia Ward - LLD, 1910 (Box 81)
  - Hufstedler, Shirley Mount - LLD, 1982 (Box 81)
  - Huxstable, Ada Louise - LHD, 1968 (Box 81)
  - Inhelder, Barbel - ScD, 1975 (Box 82)
  - Jodai, Tano - LLD, 1962 (Box 82)
  - Johnson, Laura - LLD, 1976 (Box 82)
  - Jones, Sir Robert - ScD, 1921 (Box 82)
  - Jordan, Sara Murray - ScD, 1935 (Box 82)
  - Kael, Pauline - LittD, 1973 (Box 82)
  - Kaur, Rajkumari Amrit - LLD, 1956 (Box 82)
  - Kennan, Elizabeth Topham - LLD, 1984 (Box 82)
  - Kirkbride, Mary - ScD, 1932 (Box 82)
  - Kohler, Charlotte - LittD, 1971 (Box 82)
  - Kramrisch, Stella - LHD, 1982 (Box 82)
  - Krokodilou, Koralia Afroditi - AM, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Kubler-Ross, Elizabeth - ScD, 1975 (Box 82)
  - Lathrop, Julia Clifford - LLD, 1928 (Box 82)
  - LeGallienne, Eva - LHD, 1930 (Box 82)
  - Lewis, Elma - DFA, 1976 (Box 82)
  - MacCaffrey, Isabel Gamble - LHD, 1978 (Box 82)
  - MacKenzie, Jean Kenyon - AM, 1927 (Box 82)
  - Maeztu, Maria de - LLD, 1919 (Box 82)
  - Mahoney, Margaret - LLD, 1985 (Box 82)
  - Marti Kainen, Anne Helen - ScD, 1969 (Box 82)
  - Mayer, Maria Goeppert - ScD, 1961 (Box 82)
  - Maz, Veronica - LHD, 1980 (Box 82)
  - McAfee, Mildred Helen - LLD, 1944 (Box 82)
  - McBride, Katharine Elizabeth - LLD, 1947 (Box 82)
  - McClintock, Barbara - ScD, 1958 (Box 82)
  - McCormick, Anne O'Hare - LLD, 1939 (Box 82)
  - McGinley, Phyllis - LittD, 1964 (Box 82)
  - McIntosh, Millicent Carey - LLD, 1940 (Box 82)
  - McKinley, William - LLD, 1899 (Box 82)
  - Mead, Elizabeth Storrs - LHD, 1900 (Box 82)
  - Meir, Gold - LLD, 1960 (Box 82)
  - Meitner, Lise - ScD, 1946 (Box 82)
  - Mentschikoff, Soia - LLD, 1967 (Box 82)
  - Mitford, Jessica - LittD, 1974 (Box 82)
  - Mongan, Elizabeth - LHD, 1985 (Box 82)
  - Morawetz, Cathleen Synge - ScD, 1982 (Box 82)
  - Morini, Erica - MusD, 1955 (Box 82)
  - Morrison, Toni - LHD, 1991 (Box 82)
  - Motley, Constance Baker - LHD, 1965 (Box 82)
  - Musgrowe, Thea - MusD, 1979 (Box 82)
  - Neilson, Nellie - LHD, 1939 (Box 82)
  - Nevelson, Louise - DFA, 1973 (Box 82)
  - Newcomer, Mabel - LLD, 1945 (Box 82)
  - Norton, Eleanor Holmes - LLD, 1983 (Box 82)
  - O'Connor, Flannery - LittD, 1963 (Box 82)
  - Ogata, Sadako - LLD, 1980 (Box 82)
  - Origigo, Iris - LittD, 1964 (Box 82)
  - Pantaleoni, Helenka - LittD, 1975 (Box 83)
  - Park, Marion Edwards - LLD, 1925 (Box 83)
  - Patrick, Mary Mills - LLD, 1914 (Box 83)
  - Pate, Martha Lucas - LHD, 1971 (Box 83)
  - Pendleton, Ellen Fitz - LLD, 1925 (Box 83)
  - Peterson, Esther Eggertsen - LLD, 1963 (Box 83)
  - Phillips, Marjorie - DFA, 1973 (Box 83)
  - Porada, Edith - LittD, 1967 (Box 83)
  - Porter, Katharine Anne - LittD, 1958 (Box 83)
  - Porter, Sylvia Field - LLD, 1976 (Box 83)
  - Pound, Louise - LHD, 1928 (Box 83)
  - Putnam, Bertha Haven - LLD, 1945 (Box 83)
  - Ray, Dixie Lee - ScD, 1975 (Box 83)
  - Reading, Dowager Marchioness of - LLD, 1956 (Box 83)
  - Reid, Helen Rogers - LLD, 1948 (Box 83)
  - Rich, Adrienne - LittD, 1979 (Box 83)
  - Richmond, Mary Ellen - AM, 1921 (Box 83)
  - Richter, Gisela - LHD, 1935 (Box 83)
  - Rincon, Maria Elena - LHD, 1949 (Box 83)
  - Robbins, Caroline - LLD, 1971 (Box 83)
  - Robinson, Julia Bowman - ScD, 1979 (Box 83)
  - Roche, Josephine - LLD, 1932 (Box 83)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor - LLD, 1949 (Box 83)
  - Sanger, Margaret - LLD, 1949 (Box 83)
  - Schain, Josephine - LLD, 1937 (Box 83)
  - Scharrer, Berta - ScD, 1980 (Box 83)
  - Sills, Beverly - LHD, 1985 (Box 83)
  - Simkhovitch, Mary Kingsbury - LLD, 1951 (Box 83)
  - Skard, Ase Gruda - LHD, 1983 (Box 83)
  - Smith, Margaret Chase - LLD, 1949 (Box 83)
  - Smith, Olive Watkins - ScD, 1951 (Box 83)
  - Speer, Emma Bailey - AM, 1925 (Box 83)
  - Stevens, Rise - DFA, 1970 (Box 83)
  - Stevenson, George Stanley - LLD, 1949 (Box 83)
  - Storrow, Helen Osborne - AM, 1934 (Box 83)
  - Stratton, Dorothy Constance - LLD, 1952 (Box 83)
  - Stringfellow, Ethel Grey - LHD, 1960 (Box 83)
  - Suzman, Helen - LLD, 1977 (Box 83)
  - Switzer, Mary Elizabeth - LLD, 1967 (Box 83)
  - Talichief, Maria - DFA, 1981 (Box 83)
  - Taylor, James Monroe - LLD, 1913 (Box 83)
  - Thompson, Helen Elizabeth - LHD, 1929 (Box 83)
  - Tuchman, Barbara - LittD, 1974 (Box 83)
  - Ullmann, Liv - DFA, 1980 (Box 83)
  - Underhill, Eliza Parker - AM, 1892 (Box 83)
  - Undset, Sigrid - LittD, 1943 (Box 83)
  - Usilton, Lida Josephine - ScD, 1953 (Box 83)
  - Van Doren, Irita - LittD, 1955 (Box 83)
  - Vermuele, Emily Dickinson - LittD, 1972 (Box 83)
  - Wald, Lillian D. - LHD, 1930 (Box 83)
  - Walsh, Julia Montgomery - LHD, 1982 (Box 83)
  - Wanamaker, Pearl Anderson - LHD, 1956 (Box 83)
  - Ward, Barbara - LLD, 1949 (Box 83)
  - Webster, Margaret - LHD, 1945 (Box 83)
  - Wedel, Cynthia Clark - LHD, 1972 (Box 83)
  - Wedgwood, Cicely Veronica - LLD, 1962 (Box 83)
  - Wexler, Jaqueline Grennan - LLD, 1975 (Box 83)
  - Whitton, Charlotte Elizabeth - LLD, 1955 (Box 83)
  - Wilhelmina, Princess of the Netherlands - LLD, 1949 (Box 83)
  - Wilkinson, Elizabeth M. - LLD, 1966 (Box 83)
  - Williams, Cicely Delphine - ScD, 1976 (Box 83)
  - Wilson, Margaret Bush - LLD, 1978 (Box 83)
  - Wolff, Helen - LHD, 1978 (Box 83)
  - Wooley, Mary Emma - LLD, 1910 (Box 83)
  - Wright, Mary Clabaugh - LLD, 1968 (Box 83)
  - Wu, Yi-Fang - LLD, 1943 (Box 83)
  - Yourcenar, Marguerite - LittD, 1961 (Box 83)
  - Citations for Recipients A-Z (Box 83.1)
- Series III. Board of Trustee - Committee on Honorary Degrees
  - Abbott, Berenice, 1972-73 (Box 84)
  - Allen, Hope Emily, 1945-46 (Box 84)
  - Anderson, Mary, 1940-41 (Box 84)
  - Atwater, Helen Woodard, 1942-43 (Box 84)
  - Beals, Rose Fairbanks, 1933-34 (Box 84)
  - Beard, Mary (Mrs.), 1947-48 (Box 84)
  - Anderson, Marian, 1943-44 (Box 84)
  - Arendt, Hannah, 1966 (Box 84)
  - Arnstein, Margaret, 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Barranechea, Ana Maria, 1977-78 (Box 84)
  - Baumgartner, Leona, 1954-56 (Box 84)
  - Beard, Mary (Miss), 1944-45 (Box 84)
  - Begley, Bodil, 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Bell, Kathleen, 1958-59 (Box 84)
  - Bishop, Elizabeth, 1967-68 (Box 84)
  - Blanding, Sarah Gibson, 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Blanshard, Frances, 1945-46 (Box 84)
  - Boggs, Jean, 1974 (Box 84)
  - Boulanger, Nadia, 1893-94 (Box 84)
  - Boyden, Helen Childs, 1933-34 (Box 84)
  - Bradbrook, Muriel Clara, 1964-65 (Box 84)
  - Branch, Anna Hempstead, 1933-34 (Box 84)
  - Bree, Germaine, 1960 (Box 84)
  - Brown, Adelaide, 1938-39 (Box 84)
  - Bunce, Elizabeth, 1970-71 (Box 84)
  - Bunting, Mary I., 1959-60 (Box 84)
  - Burbridge, E. Margaret, 1963 (Box 84)
  - Caldwell, Sarah, 1967-74 (Box 84)
  - Calkins, Mary Whiton, 1910-11 (Box 84)
  - Cam, Helen, 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Carson, Rachel, 1952-53 (Box 84)
  - Carus-Wilson, Eleanora, 1967-68 (Box 84)
  - Chandler, Gloria, 1966-68 (Box 84)
  - Chase, Mary Ellen, 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Chilton, Constance, 1950-51 (Box 84)
  - Clapp, Margaret, 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Cleary, Catherine Blanchard, 1972-73 (Box 84)
  - Coe, Hazel Winans, 1962 (Box 84)
  - Cook, Constance, 1971 (Box 84)
  - Coolidge, Elizabeth Sprague, 1926-27 (Box 84)
  - Coolidge, Grace, 1928-29 (Box 84)
  - Core, Gerty T., 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Cornell, Katharine, 1936-37 (Box 84)
  - Crane, Jocelyn, 1946-47 (Box 84)
  - Crawford, Cheryl, 1961-62 (Box 84)
  - Crosby, Elizabeth C., 1964-67 (Box 84)
  - Crowdy, Rachel, 1925-26 (Box 84)
  - Crozier, Catharine, 1964-65 (Box 84)
  - Curie, Madame Marie, 1921 (Box 84)
  - Dean, Vera Micheles, 1943-44 (Box 84)
  - DeForest, Charlotte B., 1920-21 (Box 84)
  - Del Mundo, Fe, 1968-70 (Box 84)
  - De Malkiel, Maria Rosa Lida, 1954-55 (Box 84)
  - De Mille, Agnes, 1953-54 (Box 84)
  - Der Nersessian, Sirarpie, 1956-57 (Box 84)
  - De Valois, Ninette, 1900-01 (Box 84)
  - Dodd, Marion E., 1935-36 (Box 84)
  - Donhoff, Marion Grafin, 1961-62 (Box 84)
  - Draper, Ruth, 1946-47 (Box 84)
  - Drinker, Sophie, 1948-49 (Box 84)
  - Duckett, Eleanor Shipley, 1948-49 (Box 84)
  - Dunn, Esther Cloudman, 1955-56 (Box 84)
  - Edelman, Marian Wright, 1966-68 (Box 84)
  - Eliot, Martha, 1948-49 (Box 84)
  - Engel, Katharine Asher, 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Farrand, Beatrix, 1935-36 (Box 84)
  - Fay, Marion Spencer, 1963-64 (Box 84)
  - Fell, Honor B., 1961-62 (Box 84)
  - Fermin-Gomez, Mercedes, 1969-70 (Box 84)
  - Fielding, Marian Ropes, 1964-65 (Box 84)
  - Fieser, Mary Peters, 1969 (Box 84)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield, 1954 (Box 84)
  - Fiske, Minnie Maddern, 1925-26 (Box 84)
  - Flanner, Janet, 1958 (Box 84)
  - Foley, Edna Lois, 1928-29 (Box 84)
  - Fosdick, Florence, 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1972-73 (Box 84)
  - Gilbreth, Lillian, 1944-45 (Box 84)
  - Gildersleeve, Virginia, 1935-36 (Box 84)
  - Goldring, Winifred, 1956-57 (Box 84)
  - Graham, Martha, 1967-69 (Box 84)
  - Grosman, Tatyana, 1972-73 (Box 84)
  - Hall, Helen, 1967-69 (Box 84)
  - Hamilton, Gordon, 1951-52 (Box 84)
  - Harris, Julie, 1955-56 (Box 84)
  - Harris, Patricia Roberts, 1971-72 (Box 84)
  - Harris, Rosemary, 1967-68 (Box 84)
  - Harrison, Anna, 1975 (Box 84)
  - Hartridge, Emelyn B., 1927-28 (Box 84)
  - Harvey, Constance Ray, 1951-52 (Box 84)
  - Hay, Elizabeth Dexter, 1967-73 (Box 84)
  - Hayes, Helen, 1939-40 (Box 84)
  - Hellman, Lillian, 1967-74 (Box 84)
  - Henderson, Julia Juanita, 1966-67 (Box 84)
  - Hewitt, Helen Margaret, 1966-68 (Box 84)
  - Hill, Edith N., 1927-28 (Box 84)
  - Hill, Justina, 1940-41 (Box 84)
  - Hines, Marion, 1942-43 (Box 84)
  - Hobby, Oveta Culp, 1954 (Box 84)
  - Hoffman, Malvina, 1938-51 (Box 84)
  - Holland, Louise Adams, 1964-65 (Box 84)
  - Hollis, Florence, 1966-67 (Box 84)
  - Homer, Louise, 1930-31 (Box 84)
  - Horstmann, Dorothy, 1961 (Box 84)
  - Howe, Julia Ward, 1910-11 (Box 84)
  - Humphreys, Eleanor Mary, 1917 (Box 84)
  - Hunt, Harriet Larned, 1948-49 (Box 84)
  - Huxtable, Ada Louise, 1967-68 (Box 84)
  - Inhelder, Barbel, 1975 (Box 84)
  - Jackson, Elizabeth Skiller, 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Jodai, Tano, 1961-62 (Box 84)
  - Jordan, Sara Murray, 1934-35 (Box 84)
  - Joseph, Mother Mary, 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Kael, Pauline, 1973 (Box 84)
  - Kane, Amanda (Bryan), 1954-55 (Box 84)
  - Kaur, Rajkumari Amrit, 1956 (Box 84)
  - Kelly, Florence, 1950-60 (Box 84)
  - Kenyon, Dorothy, 1947-48 (Box 84)
  - Kirkbride, Mary B., 1931-32 (Box 84)
  - Kimball, Everett, 1946-47 (Box 84)
  - Kohler, Charlotte, 1968-71 (Box 84)
  - Krokodilou, Koralia Afroditi, 1947-48 (Box 84)
  - Lagarde, Charlotte, 1949-50 (Box 84)
  - Lamont, Florence (Corliss), 1951-52 (Box 84)
  - Lathrop, Julia, 1920-21 (Box 84)
  - Leet, Dorothy F., 1953-54 (Box 84)
  - Lord, Mary (Pillsbury), 1943-53 (Box 84)
  - Mackenzie, Jean Kenyon, 1926-27 (Box 84)
  - Maeztu, Maria de, 1918-19 (Box 84)
  - Marshall, Dorothy Nepper, 1971-72 (Box 84)
  - Martikainen, A. Helen, 1962-69 (Box 84)
  - Marsh, Margaret Mitchell, 1938-39 (Box 84)
  - Mayer, Maria Goeppert, 1960-61 (Box 84)
  - McAfee, Helen, 1934-35 (Box 84)
  - McBee, Mary Vardrine, 1935-36 (Box 84)
  - McBride, Katherine, 1946-47 (Box 84)
  - McClintock, Barbara, 1957-58 (Box 84)
  - McClay, Ellen (Zinsser), 1952-53 (Box 84)
  - McCormick, Anne O'Hare, 1938-39 (Box 84)
  - McGinley, Phyllis, 1961-64 (Box 84)
  - McIntosh, Millicent Carey, 1939-40 (Box 84)
  - Meir, Golda, 1959-60 (Box 84)
  - Meitner, Lise, 1945-46 (Box 84)
  - Mellon, Gwendolyn (Grant), 1958-59 (Box 84)
  - Metschikoff, Soia, 1966-67 (Box 84)
  - Miller, Dorothy C., 1951-59 (Box 84)
  - Mistral, Gabriela, 1947-48 (Box 84)
  - Mitford, Jessica, 1973-74 (Box 84)
  - Mongan, Agnes, 1940-41 (Box 84)
  - Moore, Marianne Craig, 1954-55 (Box 84)
  - Morini, Erica, 1954-55 (Box 84)
  - Morley, Grace McCann, 1956-57 (Box 84)
  - Morton, Frances Hulett, 1956-57 (Box 84)
  - Motley, Constance Baker, 1972-73 (Box 84)
  - Musgrave, Thea, 1977-78 (Box 84)
  - Neilson, Nellie, 1937-38 (Box 84)
  - Nevelson, Louise, 1973 (Box 84)
  - Newcomer, Mabel, 1944-45 (Box 84)
  - O'Connor, Flannery, 1962-63 (Box 84)
  - Oettinger, Katharine Brownell, 1956-57 (Box 84)
  - Olmsted, Mildred (Scott), 1973-74 (Box 84)
  - Origo, Iris, 1963-64 (Box 84)
  - Parsons, Mary Prescott, 1957-58 (Box 85)
  - Pate, Martha Lucas, 1949; 1971 (Box 85)
  - Payne-Gaposchkin, Cecilia, 1951 (Box 85)
  - Pendleton, Ellen, 1924-25 (Box 85)
  - Petermann, Mary Locke, 1966 (Box 85)
  - Peterson, Esther, 1962-63 (Box 85)
  - Phillips, Marjorie, 1972-73 (Box 85)
  - Porada, Edith, 1966-67 (Box 85)
  - Porter, Katharine Anne, 1958 (Box 85)
  - Pound, Louise, 1927-28 (Box 85)
  - Pratt, Harriet Barnes, 1939-40 (Box 85)
  - Puffer, Ruth Rice, 1967-70 (Box 85)
  - Putnam, Bertha, 1944-45 (Box 85)
  - Raskin, Judith, 1962-63 (Box 85)
  - Reid, Helen, 1947-48 (Box 85)
  - Richards, Ellen Henrietta, 1910-11 (Box 85)
  - Richter, Gisela Maria, 1934-35 (Box 85)
  - Rincon, Maria Elena, 1949-50 (Box 85)
  - Robbins, Caroline, 1970-71 (Box 85)
  - Robinson, Julia, 1978-79 (Box 85)
  - Robinson, Mary C., 1924-25 (Box 85)
  - Roche, Josephine, 1931-32 (Box 85)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1949-50 (Box 85)
  - Salas, Irma, 1963-64 (Box 85)
  - Schain, Josephine, 1937 (Box 85)
  - Schinz, Albert, 1927-28 (Box 85)
  - Scudder, Vida Dutton, 1921-22 (Box 85)
  - Shirk, Mary Kimberly, 1949-50 (Box 85)
  - Simkhovitch, Mary K., 1950-51 (Box 85)
  - Skard, Ase Grude, 1980 (Box 85)
  - Smith, Margaret Chase, 1949-50 (Box 85)
  - Smith, Olive Watkins, 1948-51 (Box 85)
  - Soule, Theodate (Haines), 1962-63 (Box 85)
  - Stevens, Rise, 1968-69 (Box 85)
  - Stevenson, Eleanor "Bumpy", 1945-46 (Box 85)
  - Storrow, Helen Osborn, 1933-34 (Box 85)
  - Stratton, Dorothy C., 1952 (Box 85)
  - Stringfellow, Ethel, 1960 (Box 85)
  - Sutherland, Lucy, 1964 (Box 85)
  - Suzman, Helen, 1977 (Box 85)
  - Switzer, Mary Elizabeth, 1967 (Box 85)
  - Taeuber, Irene, 1959-60 (Box 85)
  - Taylor, Lily Ross, 1960-61 (Box 85)
  - Tead, Clara Murphy, 1949-50 (Box 85)
  - Thomas, Caroline Bedell, 1954-55 (Box 85)
  - Townsend, Gertrude, 1946-47 (Box 85)
  - Tuchman, Barbara, 1973-74 (Box 85)
  - Undset, Sigrid, 1942-43 (Box 85)
  - Usilton, Lida, 1953 (Box 85)
  - Van Doren, Irita, 1955-62 (Box 85)
  - Vermuele, Emily Dickinson (Townsend), 1971-72 (Box 85)
  - Wanamaker, Pearl A., 1956 (Box 86)
  - Ward, Barbara, 1948-49 (Box 86)
  - Washington, Bennetta Bullock, 1969-70 (Box 86)
  - Watters, Hyla, 1949-50 (Box 86)
  - Webster, Margaret, 1944-45 (Box 86)
  - Wedel, Cynthia Clark, 1971-72 (Box 86)
  - Wedgwood, C. Veronica, 1954-61 (Box 86)
  - Wells, Marguerite, 1933-34 (Box 86)
  - White, Helen, 1946-47 (Box 86)
  - Whiting, Anna (Young), 1964 (Box 86)
  - Whitton, Charlotte, 1954-55 (Box 86)
  - Wilhemina, Princess of the Netherlands, 1948-49 (Box 86)
  - Wilkinson, Elizabeth M., 1966 (Box 86)
  - Willard, Charlotte R., 1921-22 (Box 86)
  - Williams, Cicely D., 1975-76 (Box 86)
  - Wilson, Mira B., 1937-38 (Box 86)
  - Wolff, Dorothy, 1949-63 (Box 86)
  - Wood, Edith Elmer, 1939-40 (Box 86)
  - Worcester, Jane, 1966-68 (Box 86)
  - Wright, Mary Clabaugh, 1966-67 (Box 86)
  - Wu, Chien-Shiung, 1959 (Box 86)
  - Wu, Yi-Fang, 1942-43 (Box 86)
  - Yourcenar, Marguerite, 1961 (Box 86)
  - Zetzel, Elizabeth Rosenberg, 1967-68 (Box 86)
  - Board of Trustees Honorary Degree Nominees
    - Colson, Elizabeth, 1966 (Box 86)
    - Fonteyn, Margot, undated (Box 86)
    - Freud, Anna, 1954 (Box 86)
    - Hepworth, Barbara, 1966 (Box 86)
    - Hess, Myra, 1949 (Box 86)
    - Lehman, Lotte, 1961 (Box 86)
    - Lessing, Doris May, 1975 (Box 86)
    - Lunt, Alfred, 1967 (Box 86)
    - MacIvor, Lauren, 1960-62 (Box 86)
    - Perham, Margery, 1967 (Box 86)
    - Price, Leontyne, 1959-67 (Box 86)
    - Renaud, Madeleine, 1967 (Box 86)
    - Taussig, Helen, 1962 (Box 86)
    - Wooton, Barbara, 1965 (Box 86)
    - Wooton, Barbara, 1965
  - Convocation - Honorary Degrees
    - 1940-41 (Box 86)
    - 1942-43 (Box 86)
    - 1943-44 (Box 86)
    - 1945-46 (Box 86)
    - 1946-47 (Box 86)
    - 1947-48 (Box 86)
    - 1948-49 (Box 86)
    - 1950-51 (Box 86)
    - 1952-53 (Box 86)
    - 1953-54 (Box 86)
    - 1954-55 (Box 86)
    - 1957-58 (Box 86)
    - 1958-59 (Box 86)
    - 1960-61 (Box 86)
    - 1961-62 (Box 86)
    - 1962-63 (Box 86)
    - 1964-65 (Box 86)
    - 1965-66 (Box 86)
    - 1966-67 (Box 86)